callerr.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy - http://www.callerr.com

Privacy Policy for http://www.callerr.com 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin at callerr.com. 

At http://www.callerr.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://www.callerr.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, http://www.callerr.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user?s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
http://www.callerr.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.callerr.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to http://www.callerr.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......   
Google Adsense
